A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1909-1974; 200; 28 Cubic Feet; 69 __Boxes __28 cubic feet
  - United States - Social Sciences, 1921-1971; 200.S; 48 Cubic Feet; 120 __Boxes __48 cubic feet
    - American Municipal Association - Reports, 1935-1939; 3 items contained in folders 3630-3632. (Box 305, Folder 3630)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports, 1935-1939; 3 items contained in folders 3630-3632. (Box 305, Folder 3631)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports, 1935-1939; 3 items contained in folders 3630-3632. (Box 305, Folder 3632)
    - American Municipal Association - Pamphlet, 1942 (Box 305, Folder 3633)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports - Financial, 1934-1937; 5 items (Box 305, Folder 3634)
    - American Psychological Association - Ethical Code, 1948-1954 (Box 305, Folder 3635)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1933-1939 (Box 305, Folder 3636)
      Grant actions, correspondence, internal RF reports and memoranda
      65 pp. of documents plus two Audits of Cash transactions for the Years ending June 30, 1934 and June 30, 1935
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1933-1939 (Box 305, Folder 3637)
      66 pages of material
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1931-1933; 6 items (Box 306, Folder 3638)
      "Report of the Director, APWA, July 1, 1923-June 30, 1933" [6 pp.] "Interstate Security" [4 pp.] "Suggestions for Dealing with Unemployment Emergencies in Smaller Communities," APWA, (November 1931) [booklet, 9 pp.] "Relief of Destitution," August 1, 1932 [2 pp.] "The Administration of Public Relief," July 25, 1932 [2 pp.] "Conference on the Maintenance of Welfare Standards, November 18, 19, 20" [booklet, 24 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1936-1937; 10 items (Box 306, Folder 3639)
      "Interstate Security" [handwritten date 1936; 4 pp.] "Some New or Reorganized State and Local Departments of Public Welfare" May 15, 1936 "Note to Draftsman," December 17, 1936 [2 pp.] "Tentative Redraft of Bill for Aid to Dependent Children," December 17, 1936 [8 pp.] "Social Security, APWA Bibliography" No. 2, October 1936 [7 pp.] "Tentative Redraft of Bill for Aid to the Blind," December 17, 1936 [10 pp.] "Tentative Redraft of Bill for Old-Age Assistance," December 17, 19136 [10 pp.] "State Administered; Tentative Redraft of Bill for Old-Age Assistance," February 22, 1936, [8 pp.] "State Administered: Tentative Redraft of Bill for Aid to the Blind," December 22, 1936 [8 pp.] "Tentative Redraft of Bill for Aid to Dependent Children," December 22, 1936 [5 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1936-1937; 5 items (Box 306, Folder 3640)
      "Directory of State Agencies and Officials Administering Public Welfare Activities," January 1, 1937 [2 copies, 19 pp. each] "Trends in Unemployment Compensation," January 1937 [7 pp.] "New State and Local Departments of Public Welfare, 1937; Outlined Digest of Recent Laws," May 15, 1937 [28 pp.] "State Administered; "Tentative Redraft of Bill for Welfare Organization," January 5, 1937 [7 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1936-1937; 2 items (Box 306, Folder 3641)
      Legislative Reporting Service, No. 5, March 15, 1937 [ca. 100 pp.] Legislative Reporting Service, No. 6, April 1, 1937 [ca. 100 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1936-1937; 2 items (Box 306, Folder 3642)
      Legislative Reporting Service, No. 9 & 10, May 15 and June 1, 1937 [ca. 100 pp.] Legislative Reporting Service, No. 12 (final) August 15, 1937 and December 31, 1937 [ca. 25 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Reports, 1936-1937; 4 items (Box 306, Folder 3643)
      "Relation of Public Welfare to Medical Care Institutions," Summary of Discussion at First Annual Round Table Conference, December 1936 [16 pp.] Marietta Stevenson and Ralph E. Spar,"The Social Security Program: Legislative and Administrative Developments to April 1, 1936" [62 pp.] "Plans of Medical Care for Relief Cases in Ten Cities." (March 1936) [16 pp.] "The Legal Basis of Public Medical Care in Twelve States," (October 1936) [58 pp.]
    - American Public Welfare Association - Newsletters, 1933-1938; 10 items (Box 306, Folder 3644)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Pamphlets, 1933-1938; 6 items (Box 306, Folder 3645)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1949-1952 (Box 306, Folder 3646)
      96 pages of material
    - American Public Welfare Association - Report, 1950 (Box 306, Folder 3647)
      "A Survey of Resources for the APWA," Raymond Rich Associates, 1950 [87 pp.]
    - American Statistical Association, 1959-1963 (Box 306, Folder 3648)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget, 1934-1941 (Box 307, Folder 3649)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget, 1934-1941 (Box 307, Folder 3650)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget - Reports, 1936; 2 items (Box 307, Folder 3651)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget - Report - Financial, 1938 (Box 307, Folder 3652)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget - Journal, 1936-1941; 5 items (Box 307, Folder 3653)
    - American Statistical Association - Budget - Pamphlets & Reprints, 1935-1940; 9 items (Box 307, Folder 3654)
    - American Statistical Association - Index Publication, 1939-1941 (Box 307, Folder 3655)
    - American University - Homberger, Ludwig - (Refugee Scholar, Transportation), 1937-1943 (Box 307, Folder 3656)
    - American University - Homberger, Ludwig - (Refugee Scholar, Transportation), 1937-1943 (Box 307, Folder 3657)
    - American University - Mann, Fritz - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1935-1940 (Box 307, Folder 3658)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1934 (Box 307, Folder 3659)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1935-1936 (Box 307, Folder 3660)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1935-1936 (Box 307, Folder 3661)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3662)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3663)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3664)
    - American University - Public Affairs, 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3665)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Federal Services Data), 1938-1940 (Box 308, Folder 3666)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Latin American Program), 1937-1942 (Box 308, Folder 3667)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Latin American Program), 1937-1942 (Box 308, Folder 3668)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Latin American Program), 1937-1942 (Box 308, Folder 3669)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Weigert, Oscar; Refugee Scholar), 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3670)
    - American University - Public Affairs - (Weigert, Oscar; Refugee Scholar), 1937-1943 (Box 308, Folder 3671)
    - American University - Tesoro, George A. - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1941-1944 (Box 308, Folder 3672)
    - American University - Tesoro, George A. - (Refugee Scholar), 1941-1944 (Box 308, Folder 3673)
    - American University - Tesoro, George A. - (Refugee Scholar), 1941-1944 (Box 308, Folder 3674)
    - American University - Tesoro, George A. - (Refugee Scholar - Economics) - Reports and Reprints, 1943-1944 (Box 308, Folder 3675)
    - Anderson, Edgar - (Botany), 1942-1945 (Box 308, Folder 3676)
    - Armstrong, Barbara N. - (Health Insurance), 1935-1945 (Box 308, Folder 3677)
    - Armstrong, Barbara N. - (Health Insurance), 1958 (Box 308, Folder 3678)
    - Association of Community Chests and Councils, 1929-1931 (Box 308, Folder 3679)
    - Association of Community Chests and Councils, 1932-1939 (Box 309, Folder 3680)
    - Association of Community Chests and Councils - Reports, 1932; 2 items (Box 309, Folder 3681)
    - Association of Community Chests and Councils - Reports - Financial, 1931-1932 (Box 309, Folder 3682)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, 1944-1946 (Box 309, Folder 3683)
    - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities - Pamphlets, 1944; 2 items (Box 309, Folder 3684)
    - Atomic Scientists of Chicago, Inc. - (Conference), 1947 (Box 309, Folder 3685)
    - Becker, Joseph M. - (Social Security Study), 1951-1954 (Box 309, Folder 3686)
    - Becker, Joseph M. - (Social Security Study), 1951-1954 (Box 309, Folder 3687)
    - Behavior Research Fund, 1931-1933 (Box 309, Folder 3688)
    - Behavior Research Fund, 1931-1933 (Box 309, Folder 3689)
    - Behavior Research Fund, 1934-1935 (Box 310, Folder 3690)
    - Behavior Research Fund, 1948 (Box 310, Folder 3691)
    - Behavior Research Fund - Reports, 1931-1933; 5 items (Box 310, Folder 3692)
    - Bennington College - Polanyi, Karl - (Refugee Scholar - History Economics), 1941-1943 (Box 310, Folder 3693)
    - Bennington College - Polanyi, Karl - (Refugee Scholar), 1941-1943 (Box 310, Folder 3694)
    - Bennington College - Political Behavior, 1951-1955 (Box 310, Folder 3695)
    - Bennington College - Political Behavior - Reports, 1951-1955; 3 items (Box 310, Folder 3696)
    - Brookings Institution, 1932-1941 (Box 310, Folder 3697)
    - Brookings Institution, 1932-1941 (Box 310, Folder 3698)
    - Brookings Institution, 1932-1941 (Box 310, Folder 3699)
    - Brookings Institution, 1932-1941 (Box 310, Folder 3700)
    - Brookings Institution, 1932-1941 (Box 310, Folder 3701)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3702)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3703)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3704)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3705)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3706)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3707)
    - Brookings Institution, 1942-1964 (Box 311, Folder 3708)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1931-1937; 5 items (Box 311, Folder 3709)
    - Brookings Institution - Report, 1942 (Box 311, Folder 3710)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1945-1953; 2 items (Box 311, Folder 3711)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3712)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3713)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3714)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3715)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3716)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports, 1954-1962; 10 items contained in folders 3712-3717. (Box 312, Folder 3717)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports - Financial, 1936-1946; 11 items contained in folders 3718-3719. (Box 312, Folder 3718)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports - Financial, 1936-1946; 11 items contained in folders 3718-3719. (Box 312, Folder 3719)
    - Brookings Institution - Reports - Financial, 1947-1955; 6 items (Box 313, Folder 3720)
    - Brookings Institution - Pamphlets and Reprints, 1931-1937; 6 items (Box 313, Folder 3721)
    - Brookings Institution - Pamphlets and Reprints, 1942-1946; 5 items (Box 313, Folder 3722)
    - Brookings Institution - Pamphlets and Reprints, 1959-1963; 5 items (Box 313, Folder 3723)
    - Brookings Institution - Clippings, 1939-1961 (Box 313, Folder 3724)
    - Brookings Institution - Agricultural Relief, 1933-1939 (Box 313, Folder 3725)
    - Brookings Institution - Agricultural Relief, 1933-1939 (Box 313, Folder 3726)
    - Brookings Institution - Government Financial Policy, 1933-1935 (Box 313, Folder 3727)
    - Brookings Institution - Government Financial Policy, 1933-1935 (Box 313, Folder 3728)
    - Brookings Institution - Government Financial Policy - Reports, 1935-1937; 2 items (Box 313, Folder 3729)
    - Brookings Institution - Hamburger, Ludwig - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1940-1942 (Box 313, Folder 3730)
    - Brookings Institution - Hamburger, Ludwig - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1940-1942 (Box 313, Folder 3731)
    - Brookings Institution - International Commercial Policy, 1937 (Box 313, Folder 3732)
    - Brookings Institution - International Commercial Policy, 1938 (Box 314, Folder 3733)
    - Brookings Institution - International Commercial Policy - Reports, 1937-1938; 10 items (Box 312, Folder 3734)
    - Brookings Institution - National Recovery Act, 1933-1939 (Box 314, Folder 3735)
    - Brookings Institution - National Recovery Act, 1933-1939 (Box 314, Folder 3736)
    - Brookings Institution - National Recovery Act, 1933-1939 (Box 314, Folder 3737)
    - Brookings Institution - National Recovery Act, 1933-1939 (Box 314, Folder 3738)
    - Brookings Institution - National Recovery Act, 1943 (Box 314, Folder 3739)
    - Brookings Institution - Pribram, Karl - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1933-1939 (Box 314, Folder 3740)
    - Brookings Institution - Rosenstock-Franck, Louis - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1940-1945 (Box 314, Folder 3741)
    - Brookings Institution - Rosenstock-Franck, Louis - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1940-1945 (Box 314, Folder 3742)
    - Brookings Institution - Sternberg, Fritz - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1941-1942 (Box 314, Folder 3743)
    - Brookings Institution - Sternberg, Fritz - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1941-1942 (Box 314, Folder 3744)
    - Brookings Institution - Steinberg, Fritz - (Refugee Scholar, Economics) - Reports, 1942; 3 items (Box 314, Folder 3745)
    - Brookings Institution - Stewart, Walter W. - (Sterling Area Investigation), 1953-1954 (Box 315, Folder 3746)
    - Brown University - International Gold Standard - Historical Record, 1932-1937 (Box 315, Folder 3747)
    - Burns, Arthur - (Travel Grant, Economics), 1949-1951 (Box 315, Folder 3748)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - International Relations Conference, 1952-1955 (Box 315, Folder 3749)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - International Relations Conference - Reports, 1953; 8 items (Box 315, Folder 3750)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - United Nations Documentation, 1948-1951 (Box 316, Folder 3751)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - United Nations Documentation, 1948-1951 (Box 316, Folder 3752)
    - Catholic University - Briefs, Goetz - (Refugee Scholar, Economics), 1931-1939 (Box 316, Folder 3753)
    - Cities Census Committee, 1928-1935 (Box 316, Folder 3754)
    - Cities Census Committee, 1928-1935 (Box 316, Folder 3755)
    - Cities Census Committee - Reports and Pamphlets, 1931 (Box 316, Folder 3756)
    - Claremont Colleges - Bergstraesser, Arnold - (Refugee Scholar, German Civilization), 1937-1939 (Box 316, Folder 3757)
    - Claremont Men's College, 1940-1949 (Box 316, Folder 3758)
    - Claremont Men's College, 1940-1949 (Box 316, Folder 3759)
    - Clark University - Killian, Frederick W. - (Criminal Law Study), 1949-1951 (Box 316, Folder 3760)
    - College of William and Mary - Foltim, Edgar M. - (Refugee Scholar, Law), 1939-1945 (Box 316, Folder 3761)
    - College of William and Mary - Foltin, Edgar M. - (Refugee Scholar, Law), 1939-1945 (Box 316, Folder 3762)
    - College of William and Mary - Hampton Roads Area Study, 1944-1952 (Box 316, Folder 3763)
    - College of William and Mary - Hampton Roads Area Study, 1944-1952 (Box 316, Folder 3764)
    - College of William and Mary - Hampton Roads Area Study, 1944-1952 (Box 316, Folder 3765)
    - College of William and Mary - Hampton Roads Area Study - Pamphlets, 1944-1946; 2 items (Box 316, Folder 3766)
    - Columbia University - Anthropology, 1931-1932 (Box 316, Folder 3767)
    - Columbia University - Anthropology, 1933-1938 (Box 317, Folder 3768)
    - Columbia University - Anthropology, 1958 (Box 317, Folder 3769)
    - Columbia University - Automobile Accident Compensation - Historical Record, 1928-1946 (Box 317, Folder 3770)
    - Columbia University - Baster, James - (Economic Development Studies), 1952-1955 (Box 317, Folder 3771)
    - Columbia University - Baster, James - (Economic Development Studies) - Reprints, 1953-1955; 3 items (Box 317, Folder 3772)
    - Columbia University - Brebner, J. Bartlet - (British Industrial History), 1949-1952 (Box 317, Folder 3773)
    - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1946-1954 (Box 317, Folder 3774)
    - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1946-1954 (Box 317, Folder 3775)
    - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1946-1954 (Box 317, Folder 3776)
    - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1946-1954 (Box 317, Folder 3777)
    - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Research, 1946-1954 (Box 317, Folder 3778)
    - Columbia University - Davis, Kingsley - (Travel Grant, Population, India), 1951-1955 (Box 318, Folder 3779)
    - Columbia University - Delatour, Gottfried S. - (Political & Social Thought in Western Europe), 1948-1949 (Box 318, Folder 3780)
    - Columbia University - Economic History, 1944-1950 (Box 318, Folder 3781)
    - Columbia University - Economic History - Reprints, 1933-1945; 6 items (Box 318, Folder 3782)
    - Columbia University - Economic Planning, 1948-1950 (Box 318, Folder 3783)
    - Columbia University - Everett, Charles W. - (Travel Grant, England, Political Philosophy), 1951-1952 (Box 318, Folder 3784)
    - Columbia University - Everett, Charles W. - (Travel Grant, Political Philosophy) - Reprints, 1948-1951; 2 items (Box 318, Folder 3785)
    - Columbia University - Fosdick, Dorothy - (Political Theory), 1952-1954 (Box 318, Folder 3786)
    - Columbia University - Ginzberg, Eli - (Occupational Choice Study), 1941 (Box 318, Folder 3787)
    - Columbia University - Ginzberg, Eli - (Occupational Choice Study), 1942-1950 (Box 319, Folder 3788)
    - Columbia University - Ginzberg, Eli - (Occupational Choice Study), 1942-1950 (Box 319, Folder 3789)
    - Columbia University - Ginzberg, Eli - (Occupational Choice Study), 1942-1950 (Box 319, Folder 3790)
    - Columbia University - Ginzberg, Eli - (Occupational Choice Study) - Reprints, 1941-1943; 4 items (Box 319, Folder 3791)
    - Columbia University - Greenwich House - Historical Record, 1929-1934 (Box 319, Folder 3792)
    - Columbia University - Jackh, Ernst - (Refugee Scholar, Political Science), 1940-1946 (Box 319, Folder 3793)
    - Columbia University - Jackh, Ernst - (Refugee Scholar, Political Science), 1940-1946 (Box 319, Folder 3794)
    - Columbia University - Jackh, Ernst - (Refugee Scholar, Political Science), 1940-1946 (Box 319, Folder 3795)
    - Columbia University - Jolowicz, H. F. - (Visiting Scholar, Civil Law), 1953-1954 (Box 319, Folder 3796)
    - Columbia University - Labor Union Leadership, 1945-1954 (Box 319, Folder 3797)
    - Columbia University - Labor Union Leadership, 1945-1954 (Box 319, Folder 3798)
    - Columbia University - Labor Union Leadership, 1945-1954 (Box 319, Folder 3799)
    - Columbia University - League of Nations - Bibliography, 1944-1954 (Box 320, Folder 3800)
    - Columbia University - League of Nations - Bibliography, 1944-1954 (Box 320, Folder 3801)
    - Columbia University - Manhattanville Study, 1949-1952 (Box 320, Folder 3802)
    - Columbia University - Mosciki, Michel - (Refugee Scholar, International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 320, Folder 3803)
    - Columbia University - Mosciki, Michel - (Refugee Scholar, International Relations), 1940-1944 (Box 320, Folder 3804)
    - Columbia University - Neumann, Franz L. - (Political Science), 1952-1955 (Box 320, Folder 3805)
    - Columbia University - Nikolojevsky, Boris - (Social History), 1941-1944 (Box 320, Folder 3806)
    - Columbia University - Nikolojevsky, Boris - (Social History), 1941-1944 (Box 320, Folder 3807)
    - Columbia University - Nussbaum, Arthur - (Refugee Scholar, Law), 1933-1939 (Box 320, Folder 3808)
    - Columbia University - Nussbaum, Arthur - (Refugee Scholar, Law), 1933-1939 (Box 320, Folder 3809)
    - Columbia University - Public Finance, 1942-1943 (Box 320, Folder 3810)
    - Columbia University - Public Finance, 1944-1951 (Box 321, Folder 3811)
    - Columbia University - Public Finance, 1944-1951 (Box 321, Folder 3812)
    - Columbia University - Public Finance - Reprints, 1943-1944; 5 items (Box 321, Folder 3813)
    - Columbia University - Public Utility Rates, 1943-1947 (Box 321, Folder 3814)
    - Columbia University - Public Utility Rates - Reprint, 1941 (Box 321, Folder 3815)
    - Columbia University - Russian Foreign Policy, 1945-1949 (Box 321, Folder 3816)
    - Columbia University - Russian Foreign Policy - Reprint, 1942 (Box 321, Folder 3817)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1941 (Box 321, Folder 3818)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3819)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3820)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3821)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3822)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3823)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3824)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1944-1950 (Box 321, Folder 3825)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3826)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3827)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3828)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3829)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3830)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3831)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3832)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3833)
    - Columbia University - Russian Institute, 1951-1971 (Box 322, Folder 3834)
    - Columbia University - Sales Tax, 1933-1936 (Box 322, Folder 3835)
    - Columbia University - Sales Tax - Press Releases, 1933 (Box 322, Folder 3836)
    - Columbia University - Social Balance Study, 1947-1953 (Box 322, Folder 3837)
    - Columbia University - Social Balance Study - Reprints, 1946-1947; 2 items (Box 322, Folder 3838)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training, 1950 (Box 323, Folder 3839)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training, 1951-1957 (Box 323, Folder 3840)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training, 1951-1957 (Box 323, Folder 3841)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training, 1951-1957 (Box 323, Folder 3842)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training - Report - (Proposal), 1951 (Box 323, Folder 3843)
    - Columbia University - Social Research Training - Reports, 1953-1955; 2 items (Box 323, Folder 3844)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3845)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3846)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3847)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3848)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3849)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3850)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3851)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1928-1941 (Box 323, Folder 3852)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1942-1958 (Box 324, Folder 3853)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1942-1958 (Box 324, Folder 3854)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1942-1958 (Box 324, Folder 3855)